I got a catsuit and fingerless gloves from Elin Harness and some really cool leather accessories
for on top of the catsuit. So I think it's going to be a really cool outfit. This
for example is part of the accessory set. Already nice and shiny, golden black. Can't wait to style
this one. This is the catsuit and I'm really curious about this one because there are no
arms and this one is a first for me too so yeah I guess I'm going to get changed and I'll see you
in a sec I have to say I do like this option without the sleeves and since it should look
like a whole outfit there are some fingerless gloves which are really really high up to my
armpits basically so it doesn't look too naked without the arms. There's a
compensation and I kind of love the skin here around my shoulders and the
cleavage. I love this V cut here so I think it's a nice a nice combination.
The material is 0.4 mm latex in both or basically all three pieces and
there is a three-way zipper that runs through the crotch until here so easy
access for bathroom breaks and stuff like that and I have to say since there
are no arms and restricting the movement it's pretty comfy actually because usually when you
wear cat suits you feel like when you lift your arms there's tension on the shoulders and not
with this option of course and yes I'm saying there are no arms all the times but of course
I mean sleeveless it's a sleeveless design so don't judge me and I think I'm going to add some
accessories now let's see what's in the box okay i think these are for the wrists so small ones
and i think that might actually be belt maybe for the tights
the bra part so i'll get this sorted out and i'll be back it's like the classic combination here
with the choker, the belt and the... I put them on the upper arms, the bracelets here.
Simple and elegant. I think it's a great combination. The patent leather combination
with the latex. Everything's shiny and then gold accessories. Really, really nice. But I have some
more accessories so I'm going to stock up. Now I added the bra, the panty and the thigh belts
and it's a lot especially with the chain neck holder part here in the bra but I think it's a
night catcher. It's really you have to look at it and look at it for a long time to figure out
what is what and what is where and what part is which and whatever and I think it's kind of fun.
And also that the neck holder is a chain adds to it too. I kind of like it.
I don't need to worry that the panty is too low cut because I'm wearing a latex
catsuit beneath it that is also really cool to be honest if I would have to go
to the toilet now I would have to strip down the panty part but other than that
easy peasy and I kind of like it I would need some like ankle bracelets now or
something in gold to end the look at shoes maybe black heels with golden
soles or heels that would be an interesting one but I think it's a nice
look and it's a simple black catsuit but with the right accessories it is really
something eye-catching and more on top of that I have these linking parts where
you can actually link different harnesses together like I could attach
it for example, slippery fingers, attach it here and maybe on the belt. You can
also shorten it so everything is size adjustable with the harness and for the
catsuit I'm wearing size small by the way you can link them to the leg belt or
or to the neck. Be creative! And of course it comes as a set. So everything is matching,
everything is the same color. Initially I wasn't so sure about the bra part and I can show you boy,
I can take it off. Let me check this in the mirror. Because the bra part kind of disrupts the
the cut in the front so I think without the bra it's also really nice it's not
as full it kind of looks empty now to be honest but if you would have seen it
first without the bra then it would have looked great without the bra so now it looks
good too but yeah that is actually everything and the whole outfit and I
I hope you liked it. I definitely do.
If you liked it, then please leave a thumbs up and write a comment and subscribe to my YouTube channel here.
You can find a lot more latex videos, a lot more alien harness.
Check out the description text for the link to the shop and also my other socials and pages.
And yeah, I hope you had fun. I definitely did.
And there's nothing more to say than see you around. Have a nice day. Bye.